<resources>
    <string name="app_name">welcomeScreen</string>
    <string name="name">\tDONATION APP\n </string>
    <string name="about_us">An About Us Page is a page on your website that tells your readers all about you. \nIt includes a detailed description covering all aspects of your business and you as an entrepreneur.
        \nThis can include the products or services you are offering, how you came into being as a business, your mission and vision, your aim, and maybe something about your future goals too.
        \nYour About Us page is your perfect opportunity to tell a compelling story about your business.Even though an About Us page is one of the most important elements of a website, it is often one of the most overlooked elements.
        \nCompared to a landing page, an About Us page help you communicate a range of things:The story of your brand and why you started it.
The cause or customers that your business serves.
Your business model or how your products are sourced/manufactured.
As an important part of your website your About Us page can set you apart from your competitors in a way that can build your brand in a positive way.
        \n\nOur goal is clear: to reach a zero hunger world. To do that, ShareTheMeal connects those in need to those who want to help. Every donation to the ShareTheMeal app supports WFP programmes - from providing homegrown school meals to children, to providing families with hot meals in th aftermath of disasters.

There are 811 million hungry people in the world, but hunger is entirely solvable. We believe that together, we ca be the generation that ends global hunger

How to Write an About Us Page</string>
    <string name="title_activity_for_lg_page">ForLgPage</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
</resources>